You've heard of procrastination, putting off tasks you'd rather avoid doing until you have to, but what about precrastination?
你听说过拖延症吧，即把你不想做的事情推迟到不得不做的时候才去做，但什么是提前症呢？
The name gives a clue.
这个名字给了我们线索。"
Pre- means before, so it's the opposite – completing tasks before you need to.
Pre-"意思是"之前"，所以它恰恰相反——在需要之前完成任务。
So, why do we precrastinate, and is it a good thing, or not?
那么，我们为什么会提前做事，这是好事还是坏事呢？
Precrastination is closely linked to anxiety and neuroticism.
提前症与焦虑和神经质密切相关。
People want to finish tasks early so they don't have to worry about them any more.
人们想早点完成任务，这样他们就不用再为它们担心了。
Ed Wasserman, a professor of experimental psychology at the University of Iowa, said precrastination is "the inclination to complete tasks quickly just for the sake of getting things done sooner rather than later".
爱荷华大学实验心理学教授埃德·瓦瑟曼说，提前症是"为了尽早完成任务而快速完成任务的倾向"。
This means you're doing something early at the expense of something else.
这意味着你提前做某事是以牺牲其他东西为代价的。
That could be a physical, financial or mental expense.
那可能是身体上的、经济上的或精神上的代价。
Imagine you submit an essay a week before the deadline.
想象一下，你在截止日期前一周提交了一篇论文。
You feel a huge sense of relief that it's over, but also can't add the last-minute tips your teachers gave you.
你感到巨大的解脱，但也没能加上老师最后一刻给你的建议。
If your marks are then lower than they could be, will you feel better in the long run?
如果之后你的分数比本可以拿到的更低，从长远来看你会感觉更好吗？
Possibly not.
可能不会。
Also, if tasks are rushed, they are more likely to be less carefully planned, so results could be incomplete or inaccurate.
此外，如果任务仓促完成，它们就更有可能缺乏仔细规划，因此结果可能不完整或不准确。
But we live in a fast-paced world, so it's hardly surprising that we want to tick off tasks as soon as we can.
但我们生活在一个快节奏的世界里，所以我们想尽快完成任务也就不足为奇了。
David Rosenbaum, a professor of psychology at the University of California, believes "It should be agreed in our society that it's OK to smell the flowers.
加州大学心理学教授戴维·罗森鲍姆认为，"我们的社会应该达成共识：闻闻花香是可以的。
To be deliberate, mindful and to be allowed to slow down."
可以深思熟虑，用心感受，允许自己慢下来。"
If you think you are a precrastinator, what can you do to still feel productive?
如果你认为自己是一个提前症患者，你能做些什么来依旧保持高效呢？
Prioritise and categorise tasks.
对任务进行优先排序和分类。
What needs to be done straight away, and what can be put off?
哪些需要立即完成，哪些可以推迟？
Recognise that some tasks need breathing room – they can even benefit from it.
认识到有些任务需要喘息的空间——它们甚至可以从中受益。